http://www.helenvanwyk.com/?showMulti=OFF&cart=paypal&route=privacyInfo&page=pageMain

Helen Van Wyk . Com Remembering Helen on DVDThe Artist -- The Teacher
StudioDVD-1DVD-2DVD-3BrushesBooksGifts
ViewCart  SwitchCart
DesktopSwitchMode
ProductsHome PageStudio SeriesDVD Page 1DVD Page 2DVD Page 3VHS Page 1BrushesBooksGift SetsAll Products ArticlesWine and Music StudyHelen Van WykA Van Wyk CritiqueInterview with Helen PoliciesShippingReturnPrivacy
Www.HelenVanWyk.Com Privacy Policy
Last modified: October 4, 2007
This policy applies to all products, services and websites by Www.HelenVanWyk.Com and its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. We
adhere to the US safe harbor privacy principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement.
If you have any questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at Privacy Matters, c/o
Www.HelenVanWyk.Com, 12416 Whartons Way, Raleigh, North Carolina, 27613 USA.
Information we collect and how we use it
We offer services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us. We do not collect
information pertaining to your visit to our web site. In order to provide order fullfillment we use 3rd party clearing houses. They
are www.paypal.com, www.google.com or www.amazon.com.
Our 3rd party clearing houses provide us with information such as email address, shipping address, order status and order history.
We use this information for the sole purpose of completing your product order.
We do not receive nor solicite information
pretaining to your financial information such as credit cards or bank accounts, or any of your payment information whatsoever.
Cookies
When you visit our web site, we may send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer
that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking
general user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or
to indicate when a cookie is being sent.
Log information
Our servers do not record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. We do not maintain or log information
such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or
more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
We do not save or log any information related to your personal visit to our
site.
User communications
When you send email or other communication, we retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your
requests and improve our services.
Affiliated sites
We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites is sent to us
for the purpase of order fullfillment. We process such information in accordance with this policy. The affiliated sites may have
different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.
Links
We present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to
improve the quality of technology and customized content. No personal information is associated or stored when clicking a link.
Information sharing
We do not share, sell, rent or otherwise disclose personal information with other companies or individuals.
Information security
Our servers do not store personal information whatsoever. We use trusted and secure 3rd party clearing house, www.paypal.com for
order fullfilment as outlined in this policy.
Data integrity
We processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this policy or any
applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only
collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure
that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their
personal information whenever necessary.
Enforcement
We regularly reviews its compliance with this policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this policy
contacting us through this web site or by writing to us at Privacy Matters, c/o Www.HelenVanWyk.Com, 12416 Whartons Way, Raleigh,
North Carolina, 27613 USA. When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is our policy to contact the complaining
user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection
authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between us and an individual.
Changes to this policy
This Privacy policy may change from time to time and we expect most such changes will be minor. We will post any policy changes on
this page. If the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. Each version of this policy will be identified
at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy policy in an archive for your
review.
